TAM LE

2386 Trafalgar Dr, Biloxi, MS 39531 ♦ tam.nt.le@gmail.com ♦ 228.273.5531

Possess over 4 years of direct customer service within a variety of major fields (waitress, tailoring, and cash register clerk), including almost 2 years in the accounting field; well-versed in office and administrative assistant work, adaptive learner; maintain strong communication skills in both teamwork and customer services; passionate about analyzing data.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration in Accounting ◆ Anticipated Graduation: Fall, 2018

The University of Southern Mississippi, Long Beach, MS ◆ Phi Theta Kappa Hornor Society

Bachelor of Science in Applied Computer Science

The University of Southern Mississippi, Long Beach, MS

Associate of Arts GPA: 3.67 ♦ Graduated: December, 2016

Mississippi Gulf Coast Community College, Gulfport, MS ◆ Vice President List, Phi Theta Kappa Hornor Society

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

- Bilingual: fluent in both English and Vietnamese
- Proficient in both Windows OS and Mac OSX, Microsoft Office, POS system, Moroe System Calculator

♦ Anticipated Graduation: Fall, 2020

Associate with Accounting Softwares: HCA (Equivalent to QuickBook), and ProSeries (Tax Preparating)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Graves & Oberlies PLLC (October 2016 to Present) ♦ Bookkeeper & CPAs' Assistant

- Multitasking: bookkeeping, tax preparing, CPAs' assistant, administrative assistant, and front-desk duties
- Bookkeeping works: input monthly checks, reconcile monthly bank statements, and post monthly journal entries for: hotels, battery wholesaler, building contractors, clinics, beauty salon, and restaurants
- CPAs' assistant and tax-preparator work: familiar with tax payments and reports on www.dor.ms.gov and assist CPAs to prepare individual income tax through ProSeries
- Administrative works: organize files and folders monthly and annually, answer phone call and schedule
 appointments, receiving mails, maintaining and updating clients' information lists, preparing and sending
 annual holiday cards

Men's Wearhouse (April 2014 to October 2016) ♦ Professional Tailoring

- Minimal supervision, self-managed customers' pick-up schedules
- Prepared yearly alteration supplies' report and maintained monthly supplies' ordering forms
- High rated customer comments in providing good services and qualified alteration
- Multitasked: alteration works, checked defects or damage clothes, repaired sewing machines, and provided individual fitting services

Tokyo Express & Kim Long Restaurant (October 2013 to March 2014) ♦ Food Server/Waitress & Cashier

- Operated the frontline cash register, and prepared brief daily budget summaries
- Maintained inventory and reported the exact amount to supervisor for future supplies' orders
- Offered variable customer services: receive orders, provide suggestions, and serving in-and-out foods
- Maintained a positive atmosphere for customers and a productive environment for coworkers